coolsocialsearch.com 2017-06-06

# CoolSocialSearch - Privacy

## Privacy Policy

#### This Privacy Policy is only applicable to CoolSocialSearch

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CoolSocialSearch does not own or control, or to people that CoolSocialSearch does not employ or manage. 

#### What We Do With Information

This policy covers how CoolSocialSearch treats personal information that CoolSocialSearch collects and receives, including information related to your past use of CoolSocialSearch products and services. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

#### General

CoolSocialSearch collects personal information when you use CoolSocialSearch, when you visit CoolSocialSearch pages or the pages of certain CoolSocialSearch partners, and when you enter promotions or contests. CoolSocialSearch automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP Address, CoolSocialSearch cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. CoolSocialSearch uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

#### Children

When CoolSocialSearch has knowledge that a child under age 13 is attempting to use CoolSocialSearch, we ask the child to have a parent or guardian consent to use or otherwise not use CoolSocialSearch. 

#### Information Sharing & Disclosure

CoolSocialSearch displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.   
CoolSocialSearch does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

#### Legal Requests

We may access, preserve and share your information in response to a legal request (like a search warrant, court order or subpoena) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of the United States where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction, affects users in that jurisdiction, and is consistent with internationally recognized standards. We may also access, preserve and share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to: detect, prevent and address fraud and other illegal activity; to protect ourselves, you and others, including as part of investigations; and to prevent death or imminent bodily harm. Information we receive about you may be accessed, processed and retained for an extended period of time when it is the subject of a legal request or obligation, governmental investigation, or investigations concerning possible violations of our terms or policies, or otherwise to prevent harm.
